Darling, ever since the smile you dropped found its way into my heart
Em, ngày em đánh rơi nụ cười vào anh
has it ever crossed your mind that you would wait
Có nghĩ sau này em sẽ chờ
and give me all your naivety unconditionally?
Và vô tư cho đi hết những ngây thơ
I, someone who always sings about far-fetched things
Anh, một người hát mãi những điều mong manh
roams around to find the joys I missed
Lang thang tìm niềm vui đã lỡ
and never bothers to remind myself to forget all the uncertainties.
Chẳng buồn dặn lòng quên hết những chơ vơ
Our love is full of wistfulness expressed in the letters just written with fresh inkblots.
Ta yêu nhau bằng nỗi nhớ chưa khô trên những bức thư
It wasn’t our fault to turn a deaf ear to the heart’s order.
Ta đâu bao giờ có lỗi khi không nghe tim chối từ
It’s a pity that…
Chỉ tiếc rằng
You are no longer my muse.
Em không là nàng thơ
I am no longer the dreamy musician, too.
Anh cũng không còn là nhạc sĩ mộng mơ
Featherlight as this love is
Tình này nhẹ như gió
it has loaded my heart with scars.
Lại trĩu lên tim ta những vết hằn
The love I sang about is vulnerable
Tiếng yêu này mỏng manh
so I might as well let go of it
Giờ tan vỡ, thôi cũng đành
and put aside our tender days
Xếp riêng những ngày tháng hồn nhiên
to return them…
Trả lại…
Darling, you will soon forget our tender days
Mai, rồi em sẽ quên ngày mình khờ dại
I just hope that you will keep our memories in your heart
Mong em kỷ niệm này cất lại
and hope that you won’t have to shoulder any sadness
Mong em ngày buồn thôi ướt đẫm trên vai
Tomorrow, as you start walking on your own spacious path of life
Mai, ngày em sải bước bên đời thênh thang
Just bear in mind
Chỉ cần một điều em hãy nhớ
There is someone who used to love you to infinity and beyond.
Có một người từng yêu em tha thiết vô bờ
You are no longer my muse.
Em không là nàng thơ
I am no longer the dreamy musician, too.
Anh cũng không còn là nhạc sĩ mộng mơ
Featherlight as this love is
Tình này nhẹ như gió
it has loaded my heart with scars.
Lại trĩu lên tim ta những vết hằn
The love I sang about is vulnerable
Tiếng yêu này mỏng manh
so I might as well let go of it
Giờ tan vỡ, thôi cũng đành
and put aside our tender days
Xếp riêng những ngày tháng hồn nhiên
to give them all back..
Trả hết....
to you.
Cho em....
You are no longer my muse.
Em không là nàng thơ
I am no longer the dreamy musician, too
Anh cũng không còn là nhạc sĩ mộng mơ
Featherlight as this love is
Tình này nhẹ như gió
it has loaded my heart with scars.
Lại trĩu lên tim ta những vết hằn
The love I sang about is vulnerable
Tiếng yêu này mỏng manh
so I might as well let go of it
Giờ tan vỡ, thôi cũng đành
and put aside our tender days
Xếp riêng những ngày tháng hồn nhiên
to give them all back....
Trả hết...
... to you
...cho em